🎵 꽃들도 (Even If The Flowers) - 찬양 전주
Even If The Flowers - JWorship (Intro)
[1절] 이곳에 생명 샘 솟아나, 눈물 골짝 지나갈 때에
Here the spring of life gushes forth, As we pass through the valley of tears
머잖아 열매 맺히고, 웃음 소리 넘쳐나리라
Soon the fruit will bear, And laughter will overflow
[1절 반복] 이곳에 생명 샘 솟아나, 눈물 골짝 지나갈 때에
Here the spring of life gushes forth, As we pass through the valley of tears
머잖아 열매 맺히고, 웃음 소리 넘쳐나리라
Soon the fruit will bear, And laughter will overflow
[후렴] 꽃들도 구름도 바람도 넓은 바다도
Even if the flowers, the clouds, the wind, and the wide sea
찬양하라 찬양하라 예수를!
Praise, praise Jesus!
하늘을 울리며 노래해, 나의 영혼아
Sing resounding to the heavens, O my soul
은혜의 주, 은혜의 주, 은혜의 주
Lord of grace, Lord of grace, Lord of grace
(간주)
(Interlude)
[2절] 그 날에 하늘이 열리고, 모든 이가 보게 되리라
On that day heaven will open, And all shall see
마침내 꽃들이 피고, 영광의 주가 오시리라
At last the flowers will bloom, And the Lord of glory will come
[후렴] 꽃들도 구름도 바람도 넓은 바다도
Even if the flowers, the clouds, the wind, and the wide sea
찬양하라 찬양하라 예수를!
Praise, praise Jesus!
하늘을 울리며 노래해, 나의 영혼아
Sing resounding to the heavens, O my soul
은혜의 주, 은혜의 주, 은혜의 주!
Lord of grace, Lord of grace, Lord of grace!
[후렴 절정] 찬양하라 예수를! 하늘을 울리며 노래해, 나의 영혼아!
Praise Jesus! Sing resounding to the heavens, O my soul!
은혜의 주 예수 그리스도, 영광의 주님을 영원히 찬양하라!
Lord of grace, Jesus Christ, Praise the Lord of glory forever!
🕊️ 온 열방과 만물이 주 예수 그리스도를 영원히 찬양합니다 · 아멘
All Creation Praises Jesus Christ Our Lord · Amen